<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE article PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.3//EN" "../../../docbook-xml/docbookx.dtd"
[
<!ENTITY name "V1Search">
]>
<article id="v1search.user">
	<title>VersionOne Search</title>
	<section id="description">
		<title>Description</title>
		<para>
			The VersionOne Search (&name;) is a standalone web application that allows individuals across your organization to search for VersionOne assets across all projects.  &name; is built on top of
			<ulink
				url="http://incubator.apache.org/lucene.net"
			>Lucene.NET</ulink>, a powerful opensource information retrieval engine.  This technology also supports a rich query parser that allows users
			to create queries that mix terms, logical expressions, and wildcards to narrow their searches.    
		</para>
	</section>
	<section id="systemreqs">
		<title>System Requirements</title>
		<para>
			VersionOne: 8.0 or above
		</para>
		<para>
			Integration Server:
			<itemizedlist>
				<listitem>
					<para>Operating System&mdash;Windows 2000, 2003</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Framework&mdash;Microsoft .Net 2.0 Service Pack 1</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Web Server&mdash;IIS 5 or IIS 6, with ASP.Net 2.0 Service Pack 1</para>
				</listitem>
			</itemizedlist>
		</para>
	</section>
	<section id="installation">
		<title>Installation</title>
		<section id="install.location">
			<title>1.  Determine Install Location</title>
			<para>
				&name;  can be installed on any web server that has internet access to your VersionOne instance. 
				Exact placement should be determined by your internal software management requirements.  
				The integation server must meet the <link
					linkend="systemreqs">System Requirements</link> stated above.
			</para>
		</section>
		<section id="install.install">
			<title>2.  Install </title>
			<orderedlist>
				<listitem>
					<para>Download the &name;  binary zip using the link above.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Extract the contents to a location on your web server.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Create a virtual directory in IIS that points to the folder you extracted the files to.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Ensure that the virtual directory is using ASP.Net 2.0 Service pack 1.</para>
				</listitem>
				<listitem>
					<para>Ensure that the default document is index.htm</para>
				</listitem>
			</orderedlist>
		</section>
		<section id="install.testWeb">
			<title>3.  Test the Web Application</title>
			<para>At this point you'll want to ensure that the Web Application is working.  Open a web browser and navigate the the URL defined in step 2.  You should see the VersionOne Search web page.</para>
		</section>
		<section id="install.indexer">
			<title>4. Index your VersionOne server</title>
			<para>To index your server navigate the the Extractor subdirectory.  From this location, you need to modify the V1Extractor.exe.config file and provide your server connection information. The following table describes the 
				parameters available to you in the configuration file.
				<table
					frame="none" id="install.configure.table">
					<title>Requestor Configuration Parameters</title>
					<tgroup cols="2">
						<thead>
							<row>
								<entry>Parameter</entry>
								<entry>Description</entry>
							</row>
						</thead>
						<tbody>
							<row>
								<entry>V1Server</entry>
								<entry>URL to the VersionOne server you wish to index</entry>
							</row>
							<row>
								<entry>V1User</entry>
								<entry>A valid VersionOne user in the system specifed by V1Server.  <emphasis>Note, that the index will only contain items this user has privileges to view.  Therefore, if you use someone like ‘admin’, then the index will contain everything.  Conversely, if you choose a user that is restricted to a given project or has “Inheritor” access, you index may contain no data. </emphasis></entry>
							</row>
							<row>
								<entry>V1Password</entry>
								<entry>Password for V1User</entry>
							</row>
							<row>
								<entry>IndexDir</entry>
								<entry>Location for storing Lucene index. </entry>
							</row>
						</tbody>
					</tgroup>
				</table>
				Once configured, open a command prompt and run V1Extractor.exe. 
			</para>
			<section id="install.configure.optional">
				<title>Optional Configuration</title>
				<para>
					Schedule regular extractions to keep the index uptodate.  This can be accomplished using windows scheduler.  We recommend that the extractions occur at a time when no one is using the system
				</para>
			</section>
		</section>
		<section id="install.test">
			<title>4. Test the Application</title>
			<orderedlist>
				<listitem>
					<para>
						Access &name; through a web browser at the location you set up during installation and search for something. 
					</para>
				</listitem>
			</orderedlist>
		</section>
	</section>
	<section id="section.footer">
		<title/>
		<para>Copyright &copy; <?dbtimestamp format="Y"?>, VersionOne, Inc. All rights reserved. This document was generated <?dbtimestamp format="Y-m-d H:M:S"?>.</para>
	</section>
</article>
